greatindochinatravel.com 2015-10-07

# Asian's Life - A Journal of Travel, Society and Culture

Please note, this privacy policy applies to this website or our mobile applications (for example our iPhone, android and iPad apps) (a “Site”). If you do not accept this privacy policy and cookies notice, do not use this Site.  

Privacy notice

Information we may hold about you

• Information you have provided to us, including our websites

• Information about products and services you have ordered or enquired about

• Information provided by other companies who have obtained your permission to share information about you

• Information about your interaction with adverts and services such as registration, comments

• Information we collect using cookies stored on your device (for example, this may be a PC, phone or tablet) about your use of MailOnline and/or selected third party websites.  For more information on cookies and how to manage them, please see our cookies notice below. 

• Your IP address, this is a number that identifies a specific network device on the internet and is required for your device and is required for your device to communicate with websites

• Technical information from your device relating to the service you receive

• Information relating to the location of the device you use to access our Site.

Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

Message boards, blogs and other public forums

Please note, the Site makes message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities available to users of the Site and registered users can provide content for and participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas of our Site becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information. For more information, please click on the Site is Terms and House Rules. 

Email a friend and share this article facilities

Please note, when you use these facilities and provide us with personal data (e.g. the name and email address) of a third party, please ensure that you have their consent before giving us their details.

Location-based and user specific services

Delivery of certain content on the Site requires you to agree to the use of your location (for example to deliver content, advertising or services such as weather that need to be relevant to where you are) along with an anonymous device identifier to enable us to recognise your browser or mobile device and provide these services across subsequent visits to our Site.

To enable the delivery of these services we will use(i) the latitude and longitude of your location and (ii) your Identifier for Advertisers (IFA) code for your iPhone, or the Android ID on Android or, place a unique cookie on the browser of your device when you first visit the Site , or a similar identifier as applicable (each a “Device Identifier”). See our Cookies notice for more information on the use of cookies and Device Identifiers on our Site.

Your location will be determined either from a lookup of your public IP address (sent in the request for content to our servers) from a public GeoIP database (effectively giving us the location of your Internet Service Provider), or directly from the device depending on its capabilities and the permissions granted to access this information.

If you consent, your location and Device Identifier will be used so that we can, together with our advertisers, provide content and advertising which is relevant to both you and your location (called “Personalised Advertising”). Please see Internet Based Advertising, Advertising Services below for further information.

You can unsubscribe from these user and location based services or withdraw your consent to receiving Personalised Advertising at any time by setting the Do Not Track preference in your browser. More information about how to do this is available by visiting our controlling interest based advertising and other third party cookies page. You can also set the Limit Ad Tracking property located in the settings screen of your Apple iPhone or iPad, or by resetting your Android ID through many of the apps that do this available in the Play Store.  You can also stop all information collection by uninstalling applications on your device. You may use the standard uninstall process available as part of your mobile device.  

How we may use your information

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business which shall include (without limitation):

• Verifying your identity (for example when you return to the Site)

• Personalising your visits to the Site and developing the design and style of the Site to improve the services provided to you

• Informing you about the latest changes to the Site, or products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting

• Dealing with, and responding to you about, a comment you have submitted for or on our message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities

• Enabling you to share our content with others e.g. using our Email a friend and Share this article facilities

• Informing you if you have been successful in any Site competitions or promotions

• Compiling customer reviews

• Conducting market research

• Carrying out statistical, technical and logistical analysis

• According to your preferences, communicating (and personalising such communication) with you:

• To send you periodic newsletters about your chosen services

• To send you direct marketing.  This may include communications by post, telephone or email or SMS about us and our business partners products and services, events and special offers, including where applicable, for a reasonable time after you have ceased to be a reader of ours

• To provide you with personalised services, such as providing with you with viewing recommendations and tailored advertising.  This includes where we have agreement to store information about you on the devices you use, for example to make some of the adverts you see more relevant to you

• To provide you with location based services such as weather information based on your location

• To provide you with advertising more relevant to your interests and your online behaviour through the use of cookies when you visit our website(s)

We may share your personal information with other companies within the DMGT group of companies

Subject to obtaining your consent, we may also supply personal information about you to third parties

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business.

Updating your preferences  

• Marketing

You can opt out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the direct marketing/newsletter emails from us.  Your can opt out of marketing text messages replying STOP. Or you can use the contacting us details at the end of this privacy notice.

• Online behavioural advertising (OBA)

If you do not want to receive online advertising where this advertising is relevant to your interests, or don not want  information processed through the use of cookies, please see the section below on cookies.

Interest based advertising

Cookies used by  the A&N Media Advertising Network & Associated Newspapers.

In order to fund our websites we run advertising on them – much of this advertising is run by the A&N Media Advertising Network. To make its advertising more relevant and effective, the network uses a range of technologies provided by third parties; many of which use cookies.

Cookies are files that store small amounts of information on your computer or other device (for example, your mobile phone). None of the cookies that we use contain information such as your real name or address, so you cannot be identified personally by them. Some of the cookies used by our websites are set by us, and some are set by third parties who are delivering services on our behalf.

Advertising services

We gather anonymous information such as on the types of pages visited, and keywords searched on in order to build an overall, but anonymous, picture of interests or preferences based on individual users browsing habits so that we can offer a more personal experience. To this information, we include information relating to a user is country, region and connection type gathered from elements of the IP of the browsing device. This practice is a core method used by our group to make our online advertising more efficient for our advertisers and more relevant to consumers.

With permission from our advertisers, we also collect information about their sites, for use on their advertising campaigns. This is often called Retargeting, or Remarketing, and involves showing ads to groups of users that have, for example, visited that client is homepage.

We will also gather information, still anonymously, on the users that reach an action page on an advertiser is site. This allows us to monitor how many sales or actions we achieve for a client, and therefore how effective our advertising is.

In order to know how many advertisements we serve, how many times these are clicked, how many advertisements we show to a given user and how many customer actions these generate, we use cookies when we show advertisements on a page.

As well as our licensed ad servers, ads are also often served from third-party ad servers, such as those of media agencies, which all use cookies to track the same metrics as ours do.

For more information about interest based advertising and how to turn this feature off, please see our cookies notice below. 

Ad verification technology  

In order to protect our advertisers brands, we often use a technology that scans the page to ascertain that it is safe from profane, sensitive & potentially brand-negative topics, before serving an ad there. This process is called Ad Verification, and these technologies use cookies to count ads served, those blocked, clicked and engaged by a user (i.e. they have hovered over them with their cursor).

Safeguards and Security

No data transmission over the internet can be entirely secure, so we do not guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of the Site. However, we use reasonable endeavours to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorised access or use by using encryption technology. In addition to these safeguards, your personal information is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act 1998. This provides that the information which we hold about you should be processed fairly and lawfully, should be accurate, relevant and not excessive, not be retained for longer than is necessary and, if applicable, be kept up to date. For more information on the Data Protection Act 1998 and your related rights please see www.ico.gov.uk.

Cookies notice

You should be aware that when you use our websites, mobile sites, or mobile apps, we may collect information by using cookies.

If you had like to learn how to manage these cookies and opt in and out of different types

What are cookies and how do they work?

Cookies are small bits of text that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Your browser sends these cookies back to the website every time you visit the site again, so it can recognise you and can then tailor what you see on the screen.

What do you use cookies for?

Cookies are an important part of the internet. They make using websites much smoother and affect lots of the useful features of websites. There are many different uses for cookies, but they fall into four main groups:

(i) Cookies that are needed to provide the service you have asked for 

Some cookies are essential so you can move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for can not be provided. These cookies don not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you have been on the internet.

Here are some examples of essential cookies:

• Keeping you logged in during your visit; without cookies you might have to log in on every page you go to.

• When you add something to the online shopping basket, cookies make sure it is still there when you get to the checkout.

• Some are session cookies which make it possible to navigate through the website smoothly. However these are automatically deleted after you close your web browser.

(ii) Improving your browsing experience  

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make, such as your language or region and they provide improved features.

Here are a few examples of just some of the ways that cookies are used to improve your experience on our websites:

• Remembering your preferences and settings, including marketing preferences.

• Remembering if you have filled in a survey, so you are not asked to do it again.

• Remembering if you have been to the site before. If you are a first-time user, you might see different content to a regular user.

• Restricting the number of times you are shown a particular advertisment. This is sometimes called frequency capping.

• Showing you information that is relevant to products of ours that you have.

• Enabling social media components, like Facebook or Twitter.

• Showing related article links that are relevant to the page you are looking at.

• Remembering a location you have entered such as weather forecasts.

(iii) Analytics  

We like to keep track of what pages and links are popular and which ones don not get used so much to help us keep our sites relevant and up to date. It is also very useful to be able to identify trends of how people navigate (find their way through) our sites and if they get error messages from web pages.

This group of cookies, often called analytics cookies are used to gather this information. These cookies don not collect information that identifies you. The information collected is anonymous and is grouped with the information from everyone else is cookies. We can then see the overall patterns of usage rather than any one person is activity. Analytics cookies only record activity on the site you are on and they are only used to improve how a website works.

Some of our websites and some of the emails you might get from us also contain small invisible images known as web beacons or tracking pixels. These are used to count the number of times the page or email has been viewed and allows us to measure the effectiveness of its marketing and emails. These web beacons are anonymous and don not contain or collect any information that identifies you.

We also use affiliate cookies. Some of our web pages will contain promotional links to other companies sites. If you follow one of these links and then register with or buy something from that other site, a cookie is sometimes used to tell that other site that you came from one of our sites. That other site may then pay us a small amount for the successful referral. This works using a cookie.

(iv) Showing advertising that is relevant to your interests  

We sell space on some of our sites to advertisers. The resulting adverts often contain cookies. The advertiser uses the browsing information collected from these cookies to:

1. restrict the number of times you see the same ad (frequency capping); 

2. and help show other ads that are relevant to you while you are on our websites. This is often called online behavioural advertising (OBA). OBA is a way of using information about your web-browsing activity, collected by using cookies, to group you with other users into interest groups and show you advertisements based on those interests. The OBA data collected from cookies you get when you are on our sites is only used to show relevant ads on our sites, not on other websites. 

Sometimes our websites contain ads for our own MailOnline or Daily Mail products. These ads use cookies in the same way as described above.

So how does OBA work? Let is look at an example. Imagine you visit a website about travel. That website shows an advert and with that advert you receive a cookie. Imagine you then visit one of our websites which has an advert from the same advertiser you saw on the travel site. The advertiser will give you a new version of the cookie you received on the travel site. The advertiser can then use that cookie to recognise that you have previously been to a travel site and show you a relevant ad.

Although the OBA data collected uses your browsing activity to understand your interests, the data is anonymous and isn not linked to you as a person. Even if you log in to our websites, the OBA data is still not linked to you.

Neither we, nor the companies who show ads on our sites sell data collected from cookies to any other organisations. 

It is easy to control interest based advertising and manage your cookies if you want to. 

Device Identifiers

A Device Identifier is a tool with an equivalent function to that of a cookie which is used to target and track the effectiveness of content and advertising delivered to users of our mobile applications.

You can reset your Device Identifier at any time through the Advertising settings on your iPhone, or opt out of sending this information by setting the Limit Ad Tracking option located in the on your iPhone.
